Halime!
-Halime!
-Where are you?
My daughter!
Halime!
Alps, get in the water!
Check everywhere!
Halime!
Soldiers!
Check under the water too!
Do not come back without finding Poena!
She is still calling her Poena!
What did you do to my daughter, huh?!
What did you do to my daughter
that made her try to take her own life?
It's all because of you!
If you had not wanted
her, she would still be alive!
You killed her!
Bala.
I will kill you!
Sofia. Pull yourself together!
Pull yourself together!
We are looking for Halime!
We are looking for Halime, Bala!
Go to the left!
You will go and look for
her with your soldiers! Go!
Soldiers!
Bala.
We are looking for Halime, come on!
Halime!
Claudius and his dogs...
They are covering their tracks but...
...those fools do not know that
we will never go back before...
...we take the revenge of our innocent people.
Oghuz senses and sees every
kind of treacherous trick for sure.
We will make them learn this, Hasan brother.
For sure.
Commander Claudius. -Tell me.
Osman's Beys Koca and Hasan...
...are following us with their Alps, sir.
Good
I was waiting for them to separate
from the herd, so they would follow us.
-How many are there?
-Not many, sir.
Don't stop them.
Let them follow us.
Understood.
Halime!
My daughter!
Poena!
Poena, where are you?
Halime!
My daughter, where are you?
-Halime!
-Poena!
My Allah, protect her... Halime!
Where are you my daughter?
My daughter!
Halime!
Halime... Where are you sister?
Where?
Halime!
There are tracks here!
My Bey!
My Bey! There are tracks here!
The tracks are coming from this side.
It goes there.
And after that point...
Poena is alive!
Osman, Halime is running away from us.
What if she is not alright? What if
something bad happened to her?
Don't worry. We will split into three groups.
Bala, you will go to the
southern side with Sofia.
Orhan, you will climb to
the hill on the northern side.
What about you?
We will go this way with the Alps.
May our war be blessed.
Come on Sisters! Come on!
Come on Alps!
This is a gift from your warriors, Orlok Kucar.
Apart from this woman, huh?
She's the shahzade's wife.
A son and daughter of Osman's is enough for me.
This woman is useless for me.
Kill her.
Don't.
You care about your wife, huh?
Bey's son
Obviously, she will be useful.
Don't kill her.
If you harm me or my wife
...you should know that your fate will
be more terrible than your messengers.
Mind your own fate, Bey's son.
-Osman's daughter?
-Your warriors are after her.
Soon, she will appear before you too.
-Fatma...
-Not Fatma. Halime!
The woman called Sofia fooled everyone.
The girl they call Meryem is actually Halime.
Is Meryem my sister?
How come?
Put them inside the cage!
-Get off!
Meryem...
Get off!
How come? How come?
My noble servant Claudius
will end this alliance!
You exposed your greatest plan to
have an alliance with Osman, huh, Sofia?
Halime is going to pass away
before she meets her family.
And the alliance will end.
How is that possible?
Vile dogs.
-Gonca, are you alright?
-Yes. You?
I'm fine.
Poena, stop!
They're after me, coming.
Who are they?
Halime! Halime!
Alps, you go this way.
Halime!
-Father...
-Halime!
Osman Bey.
My daughter.
I've found you.
I've found you. Give me your hand.
Come on, come here.
Come on, girl. Everybody is waiting for you.
I can't look at you in the
eyes after what happened.
I carry your blood, but...
...my soul is a sinner.
What do you mean? Not at all.
It's not your fault.
Come on, my dear. I'm your father.
Come to me.
As long as I live, I will
always have this disgrace.
-I can't.
-No, my little gazelle.
You won't.
Let's get over this together.
Come.
Everybody is waiting for you.
Come finish our longing.
Halime!
Whoever stands against my
daughter, I will storm against them.
You and I will fight bravely now.
Father...
I'm here, my Bey!
Orhan.
-Without swords, huh, my Bey?
-Without swords.
What makes those dogs
strong is their looks, my Bey.
They wait for the enemy's
move first and then they attack.
Still, we will hit.
We will beat them.
My Bey!
We're here, my Bey!
The enemy's tricks are shattered
on the faithful chests of the warriors.
Ya Allah!
Alps, shoot arrows!
Cerkutay.
Are these who you mentioned?
Yes, my Bey.
Orlok Kucar's warriors.
What is Kucar up to, my Bey?
-Why did he attack you?
Not me. They're after Halime for revenge.
Vipers are doing what suit them again, my Bey.
With Allah's help, they won't succeed.
For sure.
As Kucar knows everything,
...he won't stop until he
gets what he wants, my Bey.
Don't worry. We'll find Halime first.
I will destroy who is trying to harm her.
This way. Come on.
Halime!
Poena!
Halime, where are you?
Halime!
Halime..
Bala Hatun! Bala Hatun!
Don't do this to me, my girl.
Halime! Halime!
“My dear! My baby!
-Poena!
Halime! Halime!
-Halime!
-Bala.
Halime!
Halime! Halime!
Hold her.
Get her up. Halime. My baby.
Halime, my dear... Open your eyes.
Bala. Bala.
Is she alive?
She isn't breathing.
Halime.
Halime. Halime, my dear.
My dear, wake up. Wake up, Halime.
Wake up, my dear.
-Bala...
Don't! Open your eyes, my dear.
Wake up, my baby.
Halime, come on. Come on.
Don't do this. Open your eyes, Halime.
Open your eyes, my dear. Halime!
-Poena...
-No, no. -Bala?
-Osman, she isn't waking up.
-Halime!
She isn't waking up. Halime?
-Halime, open your eyes.
-Halime.
She isn't waking up, Osman.
-My sister...
-Halime.
Water. Water.
Bring water!
-Alps.
-Bring water.
-My Bey, water.
-She has a wound.
-Open your eyes, my dear.
-Come on, baby.
Halime... Halime.
-She's waken up.
-She is alive.
She's alive.
She's waken
-Aunt.
She's alive.
My little bird...
-My dear.
-Bala Hatun.
-Come on.
-Thanks to Allah. Thanks to Allah.
Osman Bey.
My Halime.
Come, my daughter, come.
Come, take a breath, come.
Are you alright, my daughter? You are injured.
Every time you call me your daughter...
..it hurts me even more.
My wound is bleeding more, my Bey.
You will always be ashamed
of having a daughter like me.
Is that even possible?
You are our blood, our child.
Don't say such words, don't, my child.
Sister, come. Let's warm you up.
Alps, come and help. Bring the horses, hurry.
Come on, my child, come on, slowly.
In the name of Allah.
Come on, my daughter.
Come on, my daughter, come on.
I told you this wouldn't be easy.
Shut up Sofia!
Osman, who were those behind Halime?
Kucar.
Kucar found out about Halime.
Kucar?
He wants to prevent our alliance, huh?
So?
Do you believe me now?
What if they learned about Alaeddin?
Which way did he go, Hasan brother?
Tell me, tell me so we can find
him and cut off the head of the snake.
The tracks spread in all
directions from here, Koca Bey.
Hasan brother!
You dastard..
So, you realized we were following you.
You are right, old man.
Osman's wanderer hunters now you are my prey!
You will know who is the
hunter and who is the prey...
...when your head is on a stake, dog.
Hold on, Hasan brother, are you alright?
I'm alright, Koca Bey.
This wound won't make me fall until
I take this dastard's life, Koca Bey.
When the battle starts, go without being
noticed and inform Osman Bey, my valiant.
Soldiers, attack!
Dastard!
You can't with this wound, Hasan Bey.
Let's retreat to Tavsantepe
lose our tracks there...
...and wait for Osman Bey. Let's go!
Alps, retreat, come on!
This will show Osman Bey the
direction we are going, come on.
You wanderers, with the messenger
you sent, you will trap Osman.
No.
I don't understand, Alaeddin.
If Meryem is Halime...
...Sofia would have...
She turned her into our
enemy and sent her to us, Hatun.
She turned my sister
into a sword for her hatred.
Devil...
My Allah... My Allah, what
kind of evilness is this?
May You protect her from the
evil of these demons, my Allah.
My wrath has become a mountain.
My wrath has become an
avalanche, son of the Bey.
It's pouring down on you.
Look.
Let my sister go.
Let my Hatun go.
Alaeddin..
Osman Bey's son, the Shahzade is here.
What more do you need?
Your sister and your Hatun
will share the same fate as you.
They will stand before my great Khan Olcaytu.
If your Hatun is pregnant...
...your Shahzade will face the same fate.
That baby will share the same fate as you.
You were reading El-Medinetu'l-Fazila.
I saw you.
Tell me.
Don't you ever understand what you read?
Don't you ever take a lesson from the
command of our glorious Prophet?
He said..
"In war, do not touch women, children...
...or the elderly, even if
they are your enemies."
You know this, you know this for sure.
So you are not just a shepherd, son of the Bey?
You also have some knowledge, is that true?
Right. Right.
While at war against oppression and infidelity.
Do you think the scholar's knowledge
falls behind the Bey's bravery?
Esenbike was also a woman.
So, you didn't kill her, huh?
She killed many innocent people.
If we had her in our hands,
her blood would be halal for us.
But know this.
We did not kill her, Sofia did.
Sofia.
While not in such a battle...
...Sofia would never do this since...
...she would never want to
face my glorious Khan Olcaytu.
She wouldn't do such a thing.
You will see.
You all will see.
Meryem.
What happened to them?
-Welcome, my Bey.
-Welcome, Osman Bey. -Welcome, Osman Bey.
You still haven't said anything, Osman.
As you ordered, we placed the Alps
and strengthened the Derince outpost.
Keep protecting that place.
You still haven't said anything.
We will talk in the tent.
What happened to you? Where have you been?
Mother, what is this Sofia snake doing here?
Tell me.
Kismet.
Prepare my Alaeddin's tent.
What?
My Halime will stay there.
My sister...
Mother, have you found my sister?
Where is she? Tell me, brother.
Mother.
I will tell you, daughter. I will tell you.
Halime is here.
Your sister is standing right in front of you.
She is not Meryem. She is Halime.
What?
Mother, what are you saying?
I will explain. But right
now, your sister is very tired.
Let her rest for a bit, alright, my daughter?
Come on. Come on, my daughter.
Orhan. What's happening?
Sofia.
That snake Sofia planned
a game. She did all this.
She betrayed us, huh?
She betrayed her own blood.
She became Sofia's puppet.
Sister. My Fatma.
My sister...
Why are you saying that?
She is our sister.
She is our sibling.
No. My sister is in the grave.
She died the day my
mother found her in that river.
Everyone looks at me with doubt
They know I deceived them.
They don't know you, and you don't know them.
But we will forget about the past.
We will start again.
I have no past to forget or remember.
Poena is lost, Meryem is dead.
Halime... Halime knows nothing.
Look at me.
I am your mother, and you
are my beautiful daughter.
For now, knowing this is enough, alright?
Now go to the tent, I'll bring you a dress.
Come on, my daughter.
Mongols or others...
Whoever comes to these borders...
...the Byzantine soldiers,
according to this peace
agreement, will be under
my command, in my army.
If Bursa is attacked...
...then your Alps...
...will be under my command.
Then we agreed.
From now on, we are friends, Osman Bey.
Since we agreed on peace, I want Claudius.
Claudius is a good commander, Osman Bey.
As the Emperor said, I can
make him pledge allegiance you.
No. The blood of my martyrs is on his hands.
I will never let him join my army.
Dead or alive, I will punish
him with my own hands.
Now, as a symbol of this peace...
...you will give me his head.
If you try to oppose this...
-No, that won't happen.
Claudius, with what he did, betrayed
not only me but the Emperor as well.
Killing him won't break our peace.
It's like a dream.
If I had never left here
...what would my life be like?
You are angry with me, aren't you?
Am I angry?
If you weren't family
...I would kill you without hesitation.
You used me to enter the tribe.
To spy on us.
We shared our bread with you.
We let you join our family.
You betrayed us.
What I did cannot be forgiven. I know that.
I don't understand.
How could a person do this to another one?
I thought you were my enemy.
You kept disappearing to send messages, right?
It was you who told them
where the hidden tribe was.
-You exposed our secrets one by one.
-Yes, I did.
I did.
I did everything to kill
Osman Bey and Bala Hatun.
You also knew that my mother
didn't get burned in that cabin.
And you let us lament and mourn.
I thought my sorrow would
be gone while I watched yours.
But it hurt me more.
I thought you were my enemy.
No, no. We wouldn't do this to even our enemy.
You became Sofia's daughter.
-You...
Fatma, this is enough.
Mother, we can't trust this girl.
She's not an ordinary girl but your sister.
This girl is not my sister.
-Fatma.
-Mother, leave me.
-Don't do this, my dear.
Halime.
If you had let me die,
...everything would be easier.
We need to cauterize your wound, brother Hasan.
But we can't make a fire now.
Old man!
You will be burned.
Another fire will burn you, though.
Which fire is that?
My wrath's fire?
You Turks have a saying... What was that?
I'm a hero but it has no use?
Something like that. Attack.
...I will cut you into pieces and
make a thousand animals eat you.
It seems the pain of your wound...
...didn't bring you around.
I swear..
...I will make a wound in your
chest and cauterize it with salt!
Are you only this strong?
Hit me like a real man!
Call reinforcements.
We will need them thanks to Beys.
Do you think...
...we drew Osman Bey into a
trap by sending the messenger?
Beys, I have an offer for you.
But let's relax a bit first. Get them up.
It seems your people aren't pleased
with our agreement, Osman Bey.
Neither am I.
Yet this isn't the first time
the wolf works with a jackal.
There isn't only an agreement
but also Poena between us now.
You have no relations left with Halime's past.
When we take care of Mongolians,
we will see what happens.
I looked after her for 10 years.
There is a bond between me and her.
You can't change the past.
Before I leave, I want to see Poena.
They will look at Poena with
hatred. You can't change that.
She will be upset and sad.
You don't know what family means, Sofia.
We will heal together all the wounds you opened.
Halime will be even happier than before.
Is that why your brother Alaaddin left?
Poena will want to leave too.
Then you will have to let her come to me.
Look at me.
If you mention taking Halime away,
...I won't mind any agreements
but kill you right here.
Fatma, how is your sister doing?
Do you mean Sofia's daughter, father?
She's fine. She will be alright.
Reconsider what I said, Osman.
Osman.
-What is she doing here?
-Where is Poena?
Halime.
-My dear.
Come. Come here.
Come to me.
Praise be.
Praise be to you.
You look great.
You look perfect.
Seeing you in my mother's clothes...
You really look like her.
My dear, they hid the
truth from both you and us.
You're back to your family now. You are reborn.
Huh, my pretty daughter?
Poena.
I'm here to say goodbye.
Seeing you here like this...
...is torturing me.
Poena.
-You won't be happy here.
-Shut up before I cut off your forked tongue.
Alright.
She's yours now, Bala.
But..
If she wants to leave one
day like your son Alaaddin...
Enough!
Shut up!
I just care about Poena, Osman Bey.
If she wants to leave one day, then...
You will let her...
..come back to me, her home.
Her name is Halime.
And her home is here.
Stop dreaming, Sofia.
What you say doesn't matter at all.
-It's what Poena wants.
-Enough!
Enough! My name isn't Poena.
It's not Halime either.
I don't know who I am.
I don't know.
I'm tired.
I'm exhausted.
Come here, my dear. Come here.
Come.
Get out. Out!
Alright, Poena.
Calm down, my dear. Calm down.
It's alright now.
Have some rest now.
Have some rest.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in.
My Bey, a messenger from Byzantine is here.
Hristo, what's going on?
Mongolian armies have come
near Ankara in huge numbers.
Osman Bey, what do you think? Can we fight?
We fought against the huge many times.
What matter is..
Just do what our alliance requires.
Good.
I was about to remind you of our alliance.
We have a common enemy now.
Osman Bey.
Take care of my Poena.
Look at me.
If you don't want to be harmed
...watch your forked tongue.
Say it, Cerkutay.
We have more information, my Bey.
Mongolians are coming
to the frontiers in two corps.
One is marching in the north of
Ankara and the other one in the south.
It means they are marching
towards both Bursa and us, huh?
My Bey, even if we prove that
Sofia killed Olcaytu's children,
...their armies won't go back.
If they come to the frontiers
it will cause destruction.
Obviously, they intend to capture our lands.
Capturing lands is just an opportunity for them.
Olcaytu...
He seeks vengeance. He
wants my children's blood.
We will take more measures, my Bey.
Neither Fatma nor Halime
will leave the tribe for a while.
Alaeddin... Ah Alaeddin ah...
He set out alone.
Now his life may be in danger.
-Kanyumaz.
-Yes my Bey.
Go after him with the tracker Alps.
As you order, my Bey.
You caused division.
Even though today is a celebration for us...
...I can't even be happy
about the arrival of my child.
I think this is enough.
I am offering you something.
Don't waste your poison.
I will set you free and leave
you alive under one condition.
You will pull your men back
from the Derince outpost.
And you will allow my troops to enter there.
So you want the land that
has become Turkish land?
Did you hear that Hasan brother?
He wants that land from us.
Did you think we are those
who sell their honor for their lives?
Then there will be no easy death for you.
Will these blows defeat us, brother Hasan?
They won't, old man.
What did our ancestors say?
Stand tall.
"The horse knows the weight
of a man" they said, old man.
"The mule..
"The mule knows the burden
of heavy goods" they said.
"Wherever there is pain, the one
who bears it knows it" they said.
"Mindless heads suffer because of carelessness.
Your mindless head will suffer
because of your carelessness.
You infidel.
Tie them
I threw an apple and it rolled...
It went and leaned against the cradle.
The baby woke up from sleep.
Lullaby, my daughter, my daughter.
Lullaby, my child, my child.
Lullaby, my baby, my baby.
Lullaby, my dear, my dear.
Lullaby, my baby.
I couldn't call you "my baby".
I couldn't hug you and kiss you.
Lullaby, my child, my child.
Lullaby, my daughter, my daughter.
Lullaby, my baby, my baby.
Lullaby, my dear, my dear.
I said wrong things out of pain and anger.
But again, you were right.
Being right can cause pain sometimes.
Even if you are a Bey.
Can you forgive me. Dark Osman?
So mothers can be devastated.
Surely, even mothers can be devastated.
But what's important is...
...to stand together, supporting
each other, right, my Bala?
That's right.
We've been through many tests.
The fire that burned our hearts has gone out.
Here is where our heart's fire rests.
I still can't believe it. It feels like a dream.
All this time, she was right here.
The first day I saw her, she looked
as if she would ease all my pain.
But how did I not recognize her?
I don't understand either. How did it happen?
We always listened to the voice of
our hearts. How didn't we notice her?
She came, sat at our table.
We were together before.
But no. From now on..
...we will always be together, all together.
-All together?
What about Alaeddin? What
if something happens to him?
I sent Kanyumaz.
The Alps will find him.
Enough now. No more crying.
Come here. Enough now.
Look, we found Halime
too. The longing is over now.
The Mongols will come from one side to Bursa
and from the other side directly to us.
It wouldn't be right to split
our forces and try to stop them.
Are you saying that we will join forces with
Sofia and get into the battle together, my Bey?
Right. Right.
We will unite with the Byzantine soldiers.
When the Mongols split into two
forces, we must gather them in one place.
That's why we'll move together
with the Byzantine soldiers.
My Bey, the Byzantine soldiers
are not familiar with our army's order.
Their armor is heavy, and their mobility is low.
It will be difficult to fight
together with them in an order.
You are right.
That's why we need to train
them according to our army's order.
This duty is yours.
As you order, my Bey.
My Bey.
What if that snake Sofia plays a game again?
No.
As long as the Mongol threat is
here, Sofia cannot break the alliance.
If she tries to break the alliance...
...she knows very well that she will lose Bursa.
But after we get rid of the Mongol threat...
...she knows that our
swords will turn against her.
That's why we must be careful.
Okay my Bey.
The Claudius dog
I wonder why he opposes this alliance.
He came to defend Bursa.
But sooner or later, we will
understand what his intention is.
Koca Bey, Hasan Bey.
They left a while ago.
What is their situation?
Haven't we received news?
No news yet, my Bey.
My Poena.
My little bird.
I left my heart with you
for the future of Bursa.
Sofia.
Have you learned where he is?
Claudius took his soldiers and left Bursa.
Claudius.
You leave me no choice but to kill you.
Hristo.
You will find that fool
before he ruins my plans.
Would he oppose the emperor's decision?
He carries the heart of a devil, Hristo.
He does whatever he has in mind, no matter what.
I'm sure he is trying to do something.
But I will learn this...
...and stop him from breaking the alliance.
My sister...
...was right next to us all this time.
Alaeddin would be very
happy if he were here now.
But Alaeddin...
Alaeddin chose to leave us.
Holofira.
Lord's daughter.
Are you alright?
Orhan..
I guess I'm facing myself.
I've actually been searching
for myself for a long time.
Do you remember when
Yunus Emre told us about love?
I remember.
I never forgot.
I thought it was only the love I felt for you.
But there was another love in it.
When this love has fallen into my heart...
...I can't wear this necklace anymore.
My Holofira.
My beautiful wife...
Orhan.
...want to be Muslim.
You gave me the world.
My Hatun..
loved one...
May my Allah...
May my Allah keep us together...
...in both worlds, God willing.
Aameen.
Come, my daughter.
Ulgen Hatun is preparing the meals you love.
Thank you Bala Hatun.
Won't you call me mother?
It is not easy for me.
I thought you were my enemy a while ago.
Wait..
Wait...
She will say this word when the time comes.
Right, my beautiful daughter?
You can call me that whenever you want.
I still don't understand.
How can you trust me?
Your essence is real and strong.
Even when you were our
enemy, did you only do bad things?
Even if your mind told you
so, your heart didn't allow it.
You turned back from many mistakes.
Right.
You told Sofia the location of the secret
tribe, but then you came and informed us.
Remember the cave?
When I drew my sword against the infidels...
..you followed and fought against them with me.
You didn't leave me alone.
You didn't leave me there.
Could a traitor do this?
Maybe you knew more, but you didn't tell Sofia.
In fact, you even drew
your sword against Sofia...
...and saved Holofira and her baby.
Look, people make mistakes.
That's the nature of people.
But what's important is that you turn back
from your mistake. Alright, my daughter?
Look...
This was yours.
This brought you to me.
Now it will protect you again, huh?
Come on now, you will pour the sherbets today.
Her father wants his daughter
to pour him sherbet, huh?
Praise be.
I wonder what they fed my
little daughter in that devil's den.
But now with my meals, both her
mind and her heart will find their way.
Her soul was cooked in the devil's temple.
What will these meals do? I
hope she doesn't spread discord again.
My Fatma!
Ulgen Hatun, there's a
fake happiness in the tribe.
But it will just cause a disaster.
What that girl has done
is clear. I don't trust her.
I understand you.
Fatma Hatun.
But she's your sister.
My sister?
When I look at her, I see a traitor
who spreads lies and plans games.
Don't say that. Don't say that.
Look at me.
Don't do something crazy at the table.
Don't, my Fatma.
Tell me. What do you want from us?
Under my rule...
...a Shahzade and his
Hatun cannot eat dry bread.
This is not possible. Come to the table.
No.
Your food is forbidden for us.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Enjoy.
So you say..
"I am a scholar, I know the
special written works." huh?
Bey's son.
"Justice..
...no matter what stands against him...
..is crushing everything that stands in
the way of a person's path" says Farabi.
Was he wrong about this?
With this saying...
...didn't he describe the Mongol
who flows like a flood across the world?
Tell me.
The one who said it is right.
But the one who understood it this way is wrong.
You surely know this well.
You interpret Farabi's words in
a way that suits your interests.
If you don't like our interpretation...
...then tell us what it means.
With this saying Farabi meant...
...the justice in an ignorant city.
So...
Tell me how to be suitably fair then.
Let me say it...
...and you understand it well.
Being fair is not invading
lands like Mongols like a flood...
...turning every place
into a desert and leaving.
Being fair is, Kucar...
..improving those deserts
and bringing abundance.
It's a pity.
Osman..
...will lose a shahzade whose
mind is sharper than a sword like you.
What a pity!
Halime, you're back and
our table is more joyful now.
I don't remember much, but...
...I've always envied such tables.
Crowded and warm.
I used to dream.
Dreaming leads to reality, my dear.
We went through a lot but it's alright now.
We will have nice days. Right, Halime?
Halime is back.
Alaaddin will be back too. I know that.
Ulgen, put Alaaddin's and
Gonca's plates on the table.
I want them to see they always
have a place here when they are back.
Do I have permission, my Bey?
Come in.
Join us.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Let's get started.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Let's eat.
Okay, my Bey.
Well... Father. Mother.
Before we start eating.
...Holofira has important news to tell you.
I didn't think I would be so excited.
It's obviously happy news.
Don't make us curious, my dear.
If you approve.
..I want to become a Muslim.
Well..
Alaaddin, that's why you
joined that demon's table, huh?
Tell me.
Will the oil around your
wrists help you untie the ropes?
It will, Gonca.
It needs to help.
It has to.
Keep your eyes on that demon.
-Almost done.
-What are you saying? Stop nagging.
-Come on, come on.
-Is it untied?
Come on.
Thanks to Allah, it's untied.
Alaaddin, his back is turned.
-I got it.
-Come here, hatun.
We have to hurry. Come on.
-Come on. Alaaddin.
-I'm trying.
Come on.
Let's get out of this jackal's
den before they see us.
Come on, come on.
Let's go. Come here, hatun.
I heard a cracking sound. Get down.
Let's go, my dear. Come on.
Come on.
Prisoners are escaping!
-Alaaddin, come on.
-Come on.
Alaaddin! Alaaddin
They can never run away!
-Catch them!
-Nokers, catch!
Hurry, run!
Run, hatun!
Alaaddin, wait. Your wound...
-It's not a big deal. Come on, run!
-Alaaddin.
They're running off. Let's catch them.
They're sending a signal.
It seems there are soldiers where we are going.
This way, Gonca. Come on, hatun!
Peace be upon you.
You beat these ones. I will
slaughter the ones in the back.
Gonca
Drop your sword now or she will die.
Alright. I'm putting it down.
Don't do anything crazy.
Keep calm.
Alaaddin.
Are you alright, Gonca?
-I'm fine.
Come on then. We have to go
-Alaaddin.
-Alaaddin, stop there!
If you want to survive, stop!
My dear, now repeat what I say.
I bear witness that there is no god but Allah...
...and Muhammad is His messenger.
...and Muhammad
is His messenger.
May Allah make it sacred.
-Aameen.
Now we need to give you a suitable name.
In my dream, I was told 'you aren't Holofira'.
And they put this mirror in my palm.
This flower..
You say so, huh?
Nilufer (Lotus).
Nilufer.
The flower that blossoms in the marshland.
You left the cruel and came here.
You abandoned the evil.
The love of Islam has arisen in your heart.
Well... Then..
The name which will suit you is...
...Nilufer.
May Allah give you a long life, father.
May Allah let you be the neighbor
of our Prophet in heaven.
Your name.
..is Nilufer Hatun now.
And this is..
...a gift from me for Nilufer Hatun.
I hope your enjoy it, my dear.
Congratulations.
It must be very hard.
There is ease in every hardship.
The truth is exposed for those who know that.
My Bey.
I want to tell you something.
While I have this burden on me
...I don't feel comfortable.
Go ahead.
Alaaddin Bey.
It was a mistake that he left the
battlefield and insisted on his mistake.
But I made a mistake too, my Bey.
I was overwhelmed by my anger.
-I hit my brother.
-What did you do?
I told Alaaddin not to leave, my Bey.
But he didn't mind.
I didn't...
...want this to happen.
But it happened.
Yes, my Bey.
It happened.
The mistake you two made...
...was causing unrest.
My Bey.
While it isn't safe around...
...and Kucar is in the frontiers
..I'm worried about them.
I know Alaaddin, my Bey.
I know my brother.
If I don't go after him
...he will never come back.
With your permission, I'd
like to go see my brother...
...and settle the matter between us.
I want my brother Alaaddin to
come back to his family and tribe.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in!
My Bey, the dog called
Claudius played an evil trick.
Hasan Bey and Koca Bey lost too many.
-Where are they? -In Tavsantepe.
They've retreated to defend
and are waiting for aid.
Gather the alps.
We'll go help them.
As you order, my Bey.
Fath... Osman Bey.
Don't go.
Claudius is a dangerous man.
Don't worry.
I will ruin Claudius' game.
And then we will come back.
My daughters and wife.
They will defend our tribe.
You go after Alaaddin.
Only you can bring him back.
As you order, my Bey.
Kucar.
He must have a plan.
But we can't let him win.
Let's go.
Why are you looking, Scholar? Come here.
We'll keep going after we change your bandage.
-No.
It's just a little cut. Never mind.
Gonca, my sister Halime... That
demon is going to abduct her.
We shouldn't waste any more
time. We have to go. Come on.
-Come on.
-Alaaddin.
Vile dogs.
You took our smell?
Gonca, stand behind me.
-Be careful.
-Do not resist, Shahzade Alaaddin.
Drop your sword.
If you don't care about
yourself, care about your wife.
You dog.
-Hatun!
-Alaaddin!
Alaaddin
Alaaddin.
Get off!
-Don't touch her!
-Alaaddin!
-Leave her! Leave her!
Get off! Leave me!
-Leave her!
Leave her!
Can't you just fight bravely?
If you have courage, fight me with your swords!
-Vile dogs!
-Get off!
Leave me and I will show
you what death smells like!
Mongolians spreading death around
the world know what death smells like!
-Hatun!
-You dog.
You dog! Leave me!
Apart from your captivity, you and
I had some friendship, Bey's son.
But friendship is over.
-Leave me!
-Don't worry.
I will help you meet your sister Halime.
Kucar!
Leave my sister Halime alone! Let my wife go!
Be a real man and fight me. You vile dog!
Put them inside the cage! Now!
-Get off! Get off!
-You demon!
-Leave me.
-You demon.
-I'll kill all of you! All of you!
-Get off!
Get off!
I have a message from Claudius.
This is Claudius' messenger, Kucar.
Speak, little bird.
Claudius lured Osman
into a trap through the Beys.
Orlok Kucar..
...he is waiting for your support.
Where does he want us to support him?
-In Tavsantepe.
Excellent.
If Osman dies in this trap...
...the battle will end before it starts.
Then it will be Bursa's turn.
Nokers!
Come on!
No one will go anywhere alone
until we get rid of the Mongol threat.
Alright, my daughters?
God willing my brothers will come back safely.
God willing.
Bala Hatun, why did Alaeddin Bey leave?
Bala Hatun, huh?
You cannot even call her mother.
My Fatma.
Yes, mother?
She cannot even call you mother.
But she can call Sofia "aunt" easily.
Although she found out what she did!
My Fatma..
Now is not the time.
When will it be time, Ulgen sister?
So that you feel close to
Sofia, go and live with her!
I did not forgive her.
Forgive?
You should have killed her!
You cannot say "brother"...
...and you say "Alaeddin Bey
My brothers fell out with
each other because of you!
They fought because of Claudius!
Because of you...
...our family has fallen apart.
I am not one of them.
You are not one of them.
But you are not one of us either!
Fatma.
Stop it, my daughter.
This family cannot
overcome another sibling fight.
I don't have a sister, mother.
Fatma.
Fatma..
My Halime...
Don't be mad at your sister, alright?
She loved you very much, but now...
-She can't bear my betrayal.
Right?
She didn't think her sister could do that.
She is right.
I am a traitor.
Right, Ulgen Hatun?
I deceived everyone.
Could you trust me again if it was you?
Near Tavsantepe
My Bey.
Hasan Bey and...
...Koca Bey's Alps.
They killed him.
My Bey, when our valiants left the
outpost, their number was this many.
They all became martyrs.
My Bey.
Beys are not among the martyrs.
If they were defeated
...where are the Beys then, my Bey?
Turkmen scabbard...
It points to there.
They went this way.
But..
...infidels are after them.
But they didn't move quickly as we expected.
Do you think that's a trap, my Bey?
Claudius' goal is not killing the Beys.
His intention is to draw
them to the place he wants.
Claudius is moving contrary to what we expected.
Now I understand what your intention is.
Sofia... Sofia even gave up
on Halime to protect Bursa.
But what about Claudius? Why would
he oppose the order of the Emperor?
My Bey, I don't know if that dog is more
courageous than Sofia or more cowardly.
No, his goal is different.
Sofia wants to protect Bursa.
But Claudius wants to be the ruler of Bursa.
If he followed the Emperor's order, he
would only become the governor of Bursa.
That's why he wants to unite
with the Mongols and fight us.
Even if he is under their command...
..he will rule Bursa.
My Bey, do you say Claudius
and Kucar are allies now?
My Bey, if they are together now...
...it means this will be very
difficult. What will we do now?
No.
Claudius doesn't have many soldiers yet.
But he will surely bring Kucar to his side.
He will set a trap in another trap.
But we will attack them when
they least expect it. Hide the horses.
We will follow them on foot.
As you order my Bey. Alps!
The tracks are clear now.
There are other horse tracks too.
Apparently, they were not alone.
This is Shahzade Alaeddin's horse.
They are captured.
I should not have let him go.
I should not have.
We will find them as soon
as possible, Cerkutay Bey.
Which direction will we go?
Alaeddin's horse. It will lead us.
Release the horse.
Mother.
My daughter.
I think you should tell Alps
to guard the tribe, mother.
You know, someone who
betrays once may do it again.
She cannot be trusted.
Fatma.
Mother.
Do you expect me to forget all the
pain we suffered from? To ignore it?
Your sister didn't even want to come here.
Because of that snake Sofia,
your sister tried to kill herself.
Now you will be a big sister to
her. You won't leave her side.
In fact, I am giving you your first duty.
You will cook the herb soup together, huh?
Mother, I don't want to do anything with her.
Come on my daughter, go and take
your sister. We don't have much time.
Go, my daughter. Go.
Near Tavsantepe
There they are.
You were right, my Bey.
The dogs are keeping the Beys
prisoner here to lure us into a trap.
Claudius is not here. Let's go and kill his men.
Let's save the Beys.
We will not.
Why, my Bey?
That's why.
As you said, Claudius asked
for support from Kucar, my Bey.
And their numbers are very high.
Now it's clear that Claudius
left his position to meet them.
If we attack them with just our
swords, we cannot defeat them.
Boran, Turhan, you will come with me.
We will sneak in and take the Beys.
-Okay, my Bey.
-As you order, my Bey.
My Bey, what about me and
Abdal? What are we going to do?
You two will set traps on the way back.
We will hunt them all one
by one when they return.
Now listen to me carefully.
Did I bring you here so you
could stand there and do nothing?
Help me, so we can leave quickly.
You will choose the freshest herbs.
Not the ones that are too ripe. Come on.
I'll pick from this side.
Stop! Stop, there is a pit on that side.
You might fall.
You can fall. I don't care. But
I promised my Bala mother.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
care about a traitor like you.
Then don't tell me what to do.
Stop! Stop! Where are you going?
Stop! I told you to stop!
I said stop!
Stop, you will fall!
Stop! Stop!
What have you done?
My leg..
I didn't want to hurt you, but...
..I have to do this.
You are completely getting rid of me, anyway.
I'm leaving.
Stop, don"t go!
Stop! Don't go! Stop!
You people will never forgive me.
You will never trust me.
What have you done?
There is no place for me in this family.
Stop, Hali... Stop
I said stop!
You can't help betraying, huh?
Have they gone this way? Are you sure?
Yes, I saw it for myself
and informed you in no time.
Hush.
The bird is already off the
cage. It will be an easy job.
Let's go.
-Shahzade Alaaddin's dagger.
-This is Gonca Hatun's dagger.
Osman Bey turned out to be right.
Shahzade Alaaddin is in trouble.
We should send a message
and let him know. Come on.
Alps, watch out!
They are too many!
We need to fight hard. Come on, brothers.
Attack!
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
Allah is the greatest!
Die, dastards!
Come here.
Allah is the greatest!
My Shahzade.
This is Alaaddin Bey's dagger.
It seems the dastards abducted him.
But we will find him. We will.
Where do you think you are going?
Speak now. Where is Alaaddin?
Where is Alaaddin? I said speak!
Speak and I will send you to hell with no pain.
Come on.
Kucar is going to send him to Olcaytu Khan.
Look at me. Where is he taking him?
Where is he taking him? Speak!
Speak! Tell me Come on!
As far as I know, Mongolians...
...make their place in the most isolated spot.
How will we find them?
We will find.
Even if it costs our lives, we
will find my brother Alaaddin.
Olcaytu will never have him.
Ever.
I will find you. Alaaddin. Hold on.
Hold on.
How can explain this to mother now?
How can I explain this?
She has a death wish, obviously.
How dare you come here?
We had to make an agreement.
But my patience has limits, Sofia.
Thanks for welcoming, Bala.
I'm here to stick to our agreement.
Claudius is laying a trap
for Osman by using Beys.
Explain it. What trap?
Claudius has called reinforcements recently.
His target isn't Beys.
He'll use them as a bait for Osman.
Osman..
Alps, sisters! Bring the horses!
We have to let Osman Bey know this!
I want to do what our alliance requires,
Bala. Let me join you with my soldiers.
We should destroy Claudius together.
Bala Hatun! Bala Hatun!
-My boy, what happened?
-Fatma Hatun is stumping.
What are you talking about? Fatma?
What happened, my dear?
-Mother, she's gone.
-Who?
-Where is Halime?
-She's gone away, mother.
She said she couldn't stay here. She tricked me.
Damn it! Poena...
Halime... My dear.
Alps, you go inform Osman
Bey quickly! I need to find Halime!
Sisters, take her to the healing tent.
You go ahead, my dear. Come on.
Bala.
Bala, we can find her together
more easily. I raised her!
Bala, nobody else can
trace her better than I can.
You should pray that she's
alright! This is all because of you!
Kucar.
I'm grateful that you didn't
ignore my call for help.
I heard that you laid the trap and
was waiting for your prey, Claudius.
Well... We will share the prey, of course.
Is this...
...the reinforcement that snake called?
Koca Bey.
Are they allies?
We drew Osman Bey into a huge trouble.
What a shame!
Osman Bey.
Untie Beys, come on.
Thank you, Boran Bey.
Hasan Bey.
Koca Bey? What happened?
After we sent the messenger
to you, Claudius caught us...
...and drew you into a trap, my Bey.
Whoever did this to you
...I won't kill them before they pay for it.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Let's go and make them lose their minds, my Bey.
Well..
When they don't see you
here, they will lose their minds.
And when they come after me,
they will see what happens then.
You are wounded.
You can't fight like this.
I can't let you fight with those wounds.
Come on, wear the heathen clothes
and get out of the woods secretly.
How can we leave you, Osman Bey?
Just obey my orders. Come on.
Come on, warriors.
Let's go.
Where should I go now?
Where are you going Halime?
What do you want from me?
I swear you deceived everyone excellently.
-Stay out of my way.
-No.
I am here to take you.
Bala's most precious treasure.
I won't let you use me.
Don't worry. We will take you to your brother.
I am not going anywhere.
So you are going to tire us, huh? Take her!
That's Halime Hatun! Protect Halime Hatun!
Thank you Koca Bey.
Come on Hasan brother.
We must leave this place without
being noticed for Osman Bey's plan.
Come on.
After Alaeddin, now it's Sofia's Poena's turn.
Or, Osman's Halime.
Whatever her name is...
What a pity, Osman will die without hearing
the news that his daughter is taken prisoner.
What does this mean?
What happened here?
The cage was broken the prey ran away.
Is this how you take precautions, Claudius?
We will catch them before they reach
Osman and tell him about our trap.
Stop! Bring the horses!
Halime.
Halime!
Poena!
Mother..
Mother!
Poena!
Sofia!
Begum..
Catch her!
Come, my daughter! Sofia!
Are you alright?
You shouldn't have touched my children, Begum!
I will never let you do that!
You will die just like your children, Bala.
Here, my daughter!
Attack!
Poena!
Sofia!
Retreat!
Halime!
Sofia!
Halime, are you alright, my daughter?
Aunt..
Sofia, what did you do?
We are even Bala.
Take Poena away.
Kismet, bring the horses.
We will take Sofia to the
tribe! Come on! Get up!
We cannot, mother!
What did you say?
You called me mother!
Tell me, my daughter...
Tell me, my daughter.
Alaeddin Bey...
My brother...
...was captured.
What?
Sofia. Sofia!
Sofia!
Kucar.
What are you doing? We need to catch them!
Osman Bey and the Beys are there.
On the contrary!
You are wrong!
I am right in front of you.
Osman!
You will call me the ruler
of the state, Osman Bey!
Now that there are many of
you, you are not scared, huh?
Remember this.
Countless small numbers have
overcome countless large numbers.
I will teach you this with my furor.